[{"answer": "I think its meaning is clear", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "That could be", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You want to get married...", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You're ready now", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "And who is", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "...the whole world's out to get you..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Try my friend", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He was the orderly, during Dr. my friend's stay in Prison", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How do you think that made him feel?  What does that ,", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "...you  an orphan", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " my friend, curator of the my friend, 2 months missing", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Somewhere where his family are offering a thirty grand reward for Information, so on", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I can't think", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "We have to talk about ..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "We have to talk about ..", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A reward..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What're they on about", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Speaking of the Vacant Post", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Ah, Barne", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I have not read you your rights", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "He said, and these were his words, he our time together, because I was civil", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "He told me, he preferred to Eat the Rude. O", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.  He's found Peace", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " And have  found Peace..?", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Because you're going to help me plan a party", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'm going to do it, and you're going to catch the bouquet", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's too Hip for the Room", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't wanna go out there at ..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Speaking of which, I want you also to get us tickets for the Opera..", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "...and that is what you need to expand", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't understand", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "...why are we here in the  place...", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " We are here on sufferance.  I am here..", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Because it is exclusive... because will be here..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " ...constant humiliation.  And why", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "....because we don't have any mmm..", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "...yes...", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You want some ", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I want the money", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "The shape of a Three", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "that place.  Go.  Affirmative.  Okay, Happiness is a Green Light.  We've got my friend in the kitchen, cooking.  The dope's D.E.A.  want her on that place of some firecrackers.  Starlin", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "...these guy'll back you up", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Ah, Commendatore... you, too, admire my friend", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "If such there breathe, I'm sure you could  him...  Your reputation does you honor.", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "And how good of  to remember it. Then, this trip, then, is not a return to ..", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "And what was the trip ...", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "No, this is ..", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "That, that was ..", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "...I'm sorry....", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Indeed we were", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "...and my need for The Institution..", "docId": "hannibal_unproduced.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "And how did he do that", "qsentId": 52}]